# Giovanni Quebral

Los Angeles, California, United States



giovanni900623@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/giovanni-quebral-417760232

# **Summary**

As a CS graduate from UC Berkeley, I have over 8 years of experience working in the software industry. Currently, I work as the Senior Software Engineer on a Contract basis, where I lead a different project to successful stages. I'm deeply passionate about creating loved and trusted products that solve real-world problems.

Competencies: Javascript, React.is, Redux, Node.is, Express, Python, Flask, Data Visualization, AWS, Database,

## **Experience**



## **Senior Frontend Developer**

Spotify

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

# Full Stack Engineer

### Ognomy

Mar 2019 - Jan 2021 (1 year 11 months)

The complete sleep apnea telehealth solution - built by physicians for physicians, to cure 1 billion patients worldwide.

- · Architect front-end architecture with React, Typescript, React-Apollo, Redux
- Build iOS APP and android app using React Native, and deployed to Apple App Store and Google PlayStore
- Integrate ZoomSDK and streaming service with virtual care service providers
- Applied TDD, with Unit Testing, E2E Testing and Integration testing
- Implement marketing analytics and monitoring using Firebase Analytics Integration, HubSpot Integration

# Software Engineer

#### **Datatron**

Aug 2017 - Mar 2019 (1 year 8 months)

- Built the AI/ML automation platform frontend in React.js, Redux
- Built and provided documentation for various modular, reusable, and composable components in React.js to increase developer productivity as well as codebase maintainability
- Refactored, fixed, and pushed new code for various features spanning frontend UI to backend Python Flask and Apache Airflow services to ensure a well maintained, responsive, and flexible codebase as product goals evolve to meet various customer needs and use cases.
- Worked in a team to help vet, support, and troubleshoot pre-deployment, deployment, and post-deployment of the Datatron platform on customer networks.
- Vet and screen candidates via technical phone and onsite interviews.
- Discovered and fixed backend vulnerability that allowed for arbitrary code execution.

### Senior React Native Engineer

## Infosys

Aug 2013 - May 2017 (3 years 10 months)

- Worked with 500 fortune startups and build high quality product with different talents.
- Write maintainable and reusable code in early days which increase developer experience in the codebase.
- Write documentation for project in the best practice of 500 fortune startups.



# 

Airbnb

Mar 2012 - Jul 2013 (1 year 5 months)

## **Education**



# **UC Berkeley College of Engineering**

Bachelor's degree, Data Modeling/Warehousing and Database Administration Mar 2011 - 2014

## **Skills**

JavaScript • TypeScript • React.js • Redux.js • Vue.js • Node.js • GraphQL • REST APIs • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Git